Hello Hello Friends Namaskar Welcome to the Share Market
Video Now we
will talk You must be seeing that this is just that, so it happened to
you in this form,
okay so in such a situation you should
see here subscribe so
see here one day an officer is appointed ₹500, he
charges ₹500 for
3 months, see this was
your baseline, see this baseline
I am showing it well, see
this line on the baseline,
above the appointment of one subscriber for four months, the youth
subscribe 554 more, so
subscribe here and if ₹500 here
Kaliyug subscribe ask till where did you
not subscribe, then for this it has happened
that you will have to come here and that
option champion C,
clear it till here, how far can it go,
once we come to the support price, the
support price is ₹500, see
ICICI Prudential Limited has
its one on 29th April, so ₹500 see how many associations
of 2006  Here how many lakh 79 thousand people
subscribed 508, I am showing this after staying awake till night,
this is not subscribe 530 properly
₹500, this was happening
online in this much quantity, after that
here some special lighting was not
service, so first target 25 subscribe
subscribe 504 506, then this much is
your target, now keep in
mind and if you want to take it downwards
then what to do, it is necessary to see the support airport,
see this downwards
subscribe, see this here in the subscribe
button
270 this ₹500 chiura 300 42 lakh 31
thousand 500 and then 495 appointed three lakh
subscribe ₹500, very much subscribe, you have
subscribed to my channel,
so typing I have told you 51535
support 500 friends, this is all you get
in this video, till then Jai
Hind